[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which man originated the sentence Go west young man?", "correct_answer": "John Soule", "incorrect_answers": ["Horace Greley", "Stephen Austin", "Buffalo Bill Cody"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the  town in which the movie High Noon is set?", "correct_answer": "Hadleyville, New Mexico territory", "incorrect_answers": ["Hadleyville, Arizona Territory", "Hadleyville, Texas", "Hadleyville, Oregon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This actor, famous as Dwight Shrute on The Office, plays Rollo in Juno.", "correct_answer": "Rainn Wilson", "incorrect_answers": ["J.K. Simmons", "Jason Bateman", "Michael Scott"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "These words were said by which actor: I\u2019m a zit, get it??", "correct_answer": "John Belushi in Animal House", "incorrect_answers": ["Woody Allen in Bananas", "Jerry Lewis in Hardly Working", "Marty Feldman in Young Dr.Frankenstein"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This term refers to a division of the psyche dominated by the pleasure principle.", "correct_answer": "id", "incorrect_answers": ["superego", "libido", "ego"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The California state flag originally featured a wolf.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Named after a 19th century British surgeon and anatomist, the Bowmans capsule is located in which organ/s of the human body?", "correct_answer": "Kidneys", "incorrect_answers": ["Lungs", "Pancreas", "Brain"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How long was Mel Brooks married to his second wife?", "correct_answer": "1964 - 2005", "incorrect_answers": ["1964 - 2000", "1964-1965", "1964 - 2009"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which natural satellite of Saturn is characterized by its irregular shape, unexplained sponge-like appearance and chaotic rotation?", "correct_answer": "Hyperion", "incorrect_answers": ["Janus", "Miranda", "Oberon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these diseases is associated with vitamin A deficiency?", "correct_answer": "Night-blindness", "incorrect_answers": ["Pellagra", "Scurvy", "All of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The first artificial satellite to orbit Mars orbited the planet for 12 months beginning in this year.", "correct_answer": "1971", "incorrect_answers": ["1981", "1991", "2001"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Approximately how many pounds of food should a normal adult horse consume in a day?", "correct_answer": "15-25", "incorrect_answers": ["40-50", "5-10", "30-35"]}]